hey guys we are here with the brand new
Pokemon go TCG release the Dragonite
V-Star Premiere deck holder collection
box so if you're watching this video uh
you are just like me and you want to see
what exactly is inside of here what we
can get and is it worth it this box is
around 49.99 I have seen it like on
Amazon and a few other sellers go in for
around 40. um so make sure you do your
research and look at all of the
different places you can get it from
um and so we're gonna dive into this and
see exactly what we get now I was
planning on doing something else a
different kind of video upload this
weekend sorry for the camera Shake gosh
we'll fix that so I know if you watched
the last video
um we talked about opening up either the
uh Infernape the box or uh the
um team of Valor Pokemon go box this
thing is so big it almost doesn't even
fit inside the screen here
um so
because this was releasing I wanted to
go ahead and uh review it get into it
see all of what we're getting we may
need a different angle here as I pop
this open I so we've got an aerial view
here because this box was just so big it
wouldn't even fit
um in the current angle that we had uh
so this is what it looks like on the
inside it's a pretty nice get up here so
this is the Premier Ball deck holder I
was curious to see how big this would be
compared to the Pokeballs that you can
buy like the three pack boosters in and
it's actually a d a little size bigger
not a whole lot so again three packs
came in this ball whenever I purchased
it so this is
um a good bit bigger let's see if we can
get this open
all right so you just pull it there's no
like button to press or anything so this
is the inside of the ball so I'm seeing
this for the first time and I actually
uh brought along uh some sleeve cards
here sleeves that comes with the elite
trainer boxes that's kind of see how
they fit in here and they actually
they're actually fit um which kind of
surprised me a little bit I
traditionally expected it uh to kind of
just hold regular cards that were not
sleeved but this looks like it's big
enough to go that way if you're just
trying to prop them up but of course in
order to get the ball to close uh you're
gonna have to
fit them in like this now this is a
tighter fit but it does still kind of
fit there's still some wiggle room in
there so let's see if we can actually
close this
hopefully I didn't damage the cards
we'll find out here
um they kind of popped down a little bit
but maybe if it's full it won't do that
uh so the cards are not damaged so I
give this a solid A Plus on the uh
ability to maintain your sleeved cards
all right so out of here we do get uh
some Pokemon go codes I'll show those in
just a second and then you get nine of
the Pokemon TCG packs as well I kind of
wish they gave you 10 but you know for
the price I see why they gave you nine
um and then inside of here is the
Dragonite V promo card and behind it
once we crack this open uh there should
be the Dragonite V-Star as well so here
are the long list of codes for you to
enjoy if you want to punch those in for
Pokemon go now for the remainder of this
video we are going to crack into the
packs that we got and see if our
purchase was indeed Justified uh so here
are the Dragonite V and Dragonite V-Star
cards uh let's get this into sleeves but
first there is a code for you all right
nine Pokemon go TC Jeep hacks on Deck uh
we're gonna burn it through a few of
these here remember these packs do have
a guaranteed Hollow uh in every single
pack uh so we are looking forward to
that Pokemon go has been a
CE has been quite kind to me in the
different times that I have opened it so
far so we're looking for any new cards
that I do not have for my collection as
well of course the big Chase card being
that Mewtwo alternate art the Times
Square Mewtwo so there's a not to Amber
bomb there is a Blastoise reverse going
into a Zapdos Hollow okay so after we
burn through a couple of these uh packs
here then I'm gonna talk to you a little
bit about something that I'm planning
for the channel uh in the upcoming days
throughout the month of October there's
a code card let's do our pack trick I
think that was before I might have
messed that up
um zatu Slowbro lunatune Magikarp we
always love a Magikarp pidup Onyx Evie
Charmander oh the doof in the reverse
slot how about that and then a Mewtwo
star all right a Mewtwo V Star how about
that so in our second pack we are
pulling a V Star so now we have the
Dragonite V Star as well as the Mewtwo V
Star to go along with it see the nice
colors on that all right two packs in we
have a nice V-Star under our belt let's
continue and see what we get in pack
number three
all right
peel that back code for the folks at
home four to the front we got a psychic
energy here we got a rare candy going
through we've got our Trainer Card Magic
card a palm Charmander Evie number all
right hammerupt reverse going into a
Dragonite V how about that I've opened
several packs of uh Pokemon go so far
and I've always wanted to pull a
Dragonite still had not pulled one up
until this point that's part of the
reason why I was also excited to open up
uh this package today and sure enough we
got a Dragonite V from the pack to go
along with the Dragonite V we got as a
promo uh pretty good luck so far let's
go ahead and get into the next pack
we've got a hollow Zapdos of Mewtwo V
Star and then we follow that up with a
regular Dragonite V let's see if we can
keep look good luck rolling
code card
four to the front
steal energy and we're gonna go through
we got our spark we got our Chansey
Steelix that's actually a card I don't
have yet from this Set uh so happy to
add that one to the collection when pod
Pikachu Squirtle Melton good old badoof
[Applause]
a radiant Charizard that's my second one
uh the first one was before I started
the channel uh so I don't have video of
that this box is lit so far and we
followed that up with a hollow the last
toys wow
radiant Charizard let me get a sleeve
before my hand starts sweating and I
ruining this card all right yeah my
hands are actually sweating a little bit
after that pull pretty good I hope I
don't like Drop it like I'm starting to
shake a little bit it's not the most
valuable car in the world but I who
doesn't love Charizard and it's a
stinking shiny charizard it's a
beautiful card
um actually in better condition than the
previous one that I pulled the previous
one had a little Nick on the bottom of
this one I don't see why this one
couldn't score a really high grade I
don't see any winding around the corner
centering looks great awesome Pole right
there the radiate Charizard as our luck
continues we're gonna keep them coming
here next pack we've done really well in
every single one so far I am hoping that
uh this bundle box here that we got
today that it wasn't just like all the
hits were loaded on the first few packs
that we pulled and then
um our luck runs out but I'm not going
to speak that into existence let's keep
going with our hits think positive there
will be another hit in this pack right
here we got our Barrel we got a meltan
followed up with a reverse meltan wow
[Applause]
go the leader of Team Valor oh my
goodness my hands are starting to sweat
again from the overall craziness of this
box holy cow we got a rainbow it's the
first rainbow I've personally ever
pulled
wow all right put that to the side uh
let's just go right into the next pack
as our lucks continuing we got four
packs left and there was an announcement
that I wanted to make
um for the channel going forward for the
month of October but I'm just gonna keep
opening these packs and then whenever
the luck runs out that's when we'll talk
about what we're doing next because
right now I just want to get through the
rest of these packs
and see exactly what the rest of the
Dragonite V-Star box has in store for us
we got our Dark Energy we got a bird we
got a rare candy we got a camel we got a
fish we got another bird and then we're
going through Eevee Pikachu whoops uh
egg incubator reverse and then a
Tyranitar Hollow not as hype as our last
few packs but I love Tyranitar who
doesn't love a hollow Tyranitar card all
right three packs remain and before we
crack into those now I will go ahead and
make my announcement so you may have
noticed excuse me Mr Dragonite V Star uh
that we have a whole bunch of lost
origin uh booster bundle boxes here in
the background we've got five of them uh
so what I'm planning to do is open one
pack of lost origin every day on the
channel for the month of October I think
lost origin is a great set to do that to
get in the Halloween theme with Giratina
kind of being the mascot of this set
um so we're gonna try and do that that's
gonna be through the YouTube shorts uh
so if you want to join us along for that
ride and see what we get in our one pack
a day lost origin challenge be sure to
subscribe so you do not miss out on the
pack a day again that's going to go
through the YouTube shorts now let's get
back into Pokemon go which is just
apparently my set
um I loved playing Pokemon go over the
summer I haven't been able to play it
that much
um since the fall starting coming on but
I love the game and when this set was
first announced there's a nice
Charmeleon I was all for it uh very
first ETB I bought for it had a radiant
chocolate oh my God
the first box had a radiant Charizard
and now this one here has already a
Charizard and now we have a radiant
Blastoise follow by a hollow Snorlax
what is
or I'm speechless
oh my gosh radiant Blastoise let's bring
our old Power radiant Charizard well it
needs a Venusaur we got two packs left I
wanted to come into here hoping for that
alt art Mewtwo but forget the all art
Mewtwo at this point how about we get a
radiant Venusaur to finish off all three
Radiance that you can get in the Pokemon
go set
my goodness my fingers are so sweaty at
this point I swear it's getting hard to
rip open these packs all right come on
baby
peeling it back yet again here we are
code card
Folks at home four to the front start
with our leaf green energy the Lunatone
the Ivysaur the pokestop RO pal by doof
Charmander we love them eight Palm
Bulbasaur we need your Evolution going
into the Melt hand and then a Gyarados
not the worst Hollow in the world no
radiant we're gonna go right into our
final pack for today not gonna waste any
time whatsoever tail it back all right
final pack of this opening my goodness
my stamina meter is about empty after
all of the hype of this box I still am
speechless from the amount of poles we
have gotten here now if you get this
same amount of pulls in every Dragonite
V-Star box then it's a win it's a must
buy but of course Pokemon cards they are
random um so do keep that in mind I had
a whole bunch of success here uh the
nice reverse Lapras but not every box is
going to be guaranteed with all the hits
let's bring it home Sylveon all right I
think I already have one of those but it
is all right so we had our two
guaranteed promo cards a nice Dragonite
V and the Dragonite V Star and then the
hits from the pack we got some nice
Hollows some nice reverses but we got
two of the three radiant cards in one
box
that just blows me away and then we also
got the Mewtwo V Star a nice Dragonite V
and then the rainbow trainer Candela as
well
I I've never had this much success in
one purchase so there you have it that
is what is inside the Dragonite V-Star
uh Premiere deck holder box let me know
in the comments if you are planning on
picking this up if every box was as hype
as this one then they're gonna fly off
the shelves again be sure to subscribe
so that you do not miss out on the one
pack a day for the month of October lost
origin challenge we're gonna be
uploading one pack every single day for
the whole next month and if this opening
was any indication any foreshadowing of
the luck that we might potentially have
in that lost origin challenge you are
not going to want to miss it and to be
honest I don't even know if I'm mentally
prepared for it thank you guys for
watching and stopping by today leave a
like if you enjoyed today's craziness
and I will see you guys next time and
for the entire month of October